{
    "id": "68b205d2c1bd40e0b9993f258fa14e76",
    "title": "Omission | Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I might can be able to help.",
            "description": "Can should be removed. The sentence should read: I might be able to help.",
            "answers": [
                "might",
                "can",
                "able"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I came as much quickly as I could.",
            "description": "Before adjectives and adverbs, as is used without much.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "much",
                "quickly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I donâ€™t care how much expensive that laptop is. I am going to buy it.",
            "description": "Before adjectives and adverbs how is used without much.",
            "answers": [
                "how",
                "much",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You are quite rather a nuisance.",
            "description": "Quite and rather have very similar meanings. Use only one of them in a sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "quite",
                "rather",
                "Either quite or rather"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Do not talk such a nonsense!",
            "description": "Such is used without a before uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Such",
                "A"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been to quite too many countries recently.",
            "description": "Quite should be removed. Quite cannot modify too many or too much.",
            "answers": [
                "quite",
                "too",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Most of people do not understand philosophy.",
            "description": "We use most without of before a noun without a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Of",
                "Do"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have read all six of novels by Jane Austen.",
            "description": "Of is omitted before a noun without a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "all",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Although I was not interested in the lecture, but I sat through it.",
            "description": "Although and but have very similar meanings. Use only one of them in a sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "but",
                "Either although or but"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Though he started early but he arrived last.",
            "description": "Though and but have very similar meanings. Use only one of them in a sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "but",
                "Either though or but"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It is a small house. Besides, it also needs a lot of repairs.",
            "description": "Besides and also mean the same. Use only one of them in a sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "also",
                "a",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will never forget meeting you on that afternoon.",
            "description": "Prepositions are not normally used before expressions beginning with next or last. ",
            "answers": [
                "never",
                "on",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}